VOLODYMYR TEREBUS

tvolodimir@gmail.com - +380632276019 - Kyiv, Ukraine - https://www.linkedin.com/in/tvolodimir

ABOUT

Senior Software Engineer

I like very TS, JS, C# languages, and I am skilled in Software, Web and Game Development. I have an education in CS, mathematics, and physics. Sure, I have participated in all stages of the software development life cycle. I have led the design, development, and deployment of many projects. I have experience both with frontend and backend. Also, I worked with distributed teams and managers.

EDUCATION

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

MS Faculty of Computer Science and Cybernetics

Sep 2004 – Jun 2010 Kyiv, Ukraine

SKILLS

- Languages: English intermediate, Ukrainian native
- Domains: Software Development, Web Development, Game Development
- General skills: OOP/OOD/S.O.L.I.D principles, Software design/architecture patterns, Git Flow, CI/CD, UML
- JavaScript and libraries: ES5, ES6,.., ES2019, TypeScript, Node.JS, AngularJS, React, Angular, PixiJS, Firebase, Electron, RxJS, MobX, Redux, Immer
- Web technologies anf APIs: HTTP, OAUTH, CORS, HTML, CSS, SASS, PostCSS, PWA, HTTP caching, Responsive design, Adaptive design, CSSOM, Canvas API, DOM, IndexedDB, Web Animations, Web Audio API, Web Workers, WebGL, WebSocket API
- Tools: Git, SVN, Jira, Postman, TeamCity, Jenkins, Fiddler2, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Webstorm
- Web tools: Grunt, Gulp.js, rollup.js, Webpack, npm, pnpm, lint-staged, TSLint, Prettier
- .NET: C#, ASP.NET (WebForm, WebAPI), MSSQL, WCF, WinForms, ADO.NET, Entity Framework, XNA, T-SQL
- Unity: cross platform development, publishing to stores, debugging and optimizing, writing native plugins and editor extensions
- Personal skills: Critical Thinking, Problem-Solving, Attention to Detail, Responsibility, Team leading
- Responsibilities: requirements gathering, software designing, tech stack researching, code-reviewing, mentoring, interviewing candidates

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digicode (iSoftBet)

Senior Software Engineer

Jun 2017 – Present Kyiv, Ukraine

- have a leading role with responsibilities of application architect/tech lead
- build a pluggable, extensible, multiplatform standalone application with its own framework implementation
- · work with Electron, ts, react, angular, monorepo

- · reviewing PR from the dev team
- · am in charge of requirement gathering, research and design phases

Digicode Feb 2018 - Sep 2019 Kyiv, Ukraine

Front-end practice lead

- · was in charge of all the web outsourcing teams
- · was interviewing the candidates for the company
- · was reviewing PR from the web teams
- did mentoring
- was creating and implementing best practices/processes into web development life cycle
- · was writing tech articles

Digicode Jun 2015 – Jun 2017 Unity Developer Kyiv, Ukraine

- · have developed bunch of games for mobile platforms
- · was in charge of initializing projects from scratch
- · took participation in deployment into production, maintenance
- was working in teams with 2-5 dev

Digicode Apr 2015 - Jun 2017 Front-end Developer Kyiv, Ukraine

- · have developed and was supporting html games for mobile, desktop and facebook
- was working in teams of 2-4 dev
- · worked with various web frameworks, Vanilla JS, web APIs and tools, Node.js
- · have developed a serverless supporting system for websites and back office for operators over Firebase

Digicode Sep 2012 - Apr 2015 .NET Developer Kyiv, Ukraine

- was designing, developing and maintaining projects built on .NET ecosystem (ASP.NET, ASP WebForm, Windows services, MSSQL)
- · was involved into back-end and front-end development

UMG Sep 2010 - Sep 2012 .NET developer Kyiv, Ukraine

- was developing and supporting bunch of applications for marketing research
- worked with C#, MSSQL, WinForms, .Net Remoting, SIP, IL, MS Office, HTML, CSS, JS, ASP.NET
- · worked in team of 3 dev

resume last edited at MAR 2020